{
    "games": [
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Adenine always pairs with:",
                    "content": [
		                "thymine",
		                "cytosine",
		                "guanine",
		                "ribose"
		            ],
                    "correct": 0
		        },
                {
                    "question": "What is the process when DNA makes a copy of itself?",
                    "content": [
		                "synthesis",
		                "replication",
		                "transcription",
		                "translation"
		            ],
                    "correct": 1
		        },
                {
                    "question": "The sugar found in DNA is:",
                    "content": [
		                "dextrose",
		                "ribose",
		                "deoxyribose",
		                "glucose"
		            ],
                    "correct": 2
		        },
                {
                    "question": "Three nucleotides produce:",
                    "content": [
		                "3 amino acids",
		                "1 amino acid",
		                "mRNA",
		                "1 protein"
		            ],
                    "correct": 1
		        },
                {
                    "question": "What is the process when DNA is converted to mRNA is:",
                    "content": [
		                "synthesis",
		                "replication",
		                "transcription",
		                "translation"
		            ],
                    "correct": 2
		        },
                {
                    "correct": 3,
                    "content": [
				        "synthesis",
				        "replication",
				        "transcription",
				        "translation"
				    ],
                    "question": "What is the process when mRNA is converted to protein?"
				},
                {
                    "correct": 3,
                    "content": [
				        "the infrared light kills bacteria in the body",
				        "resistance power increases",
				        "the pigment cells in the skin get stimulated and produce a healthy tan",
				        "the ultraviolet rays convert skin oil into Vitamin D"
				    ],
                    "question": "Exposure to sunlight helps a person improve his health because"
				},
                {
                    "correct": 3,
                    "content": [
				        "11",
				        "42",
				        "13",
				        "23"
				    ],
                    "question": "What are the pairs of chromosomes in humans?"
				},
                {
                    "correct": 2,
                    "content": [
				        "protein",
				        "cell",
				        "genetic materials",
				        "organ"
				    ],
                    "question": "What does PCR detect?"
				},
                {
                    "correct": 3,
                    "content": [
				        "cell membrane",
				        "cytoplasm",
				        "nucleus",
				        "all of above"
				    ],
                    "question": "What are the main component of cells?"
				},
                {
                    "correct": 3,
                    "content": [
				        "DNA analysis tool",
				        "RNA analysis tool",
				        "can use for gene expression",
				        "all of above"
				    ],
                    "question": "What is real-time PCR?"
				},
                {
                    "correct": 0,
                    "content": [
				        "Watson and Crick",
				        "Robert Hooke",
				        "Linus Pauling",
				        "Max von Laue"
				    ],
                    "question": "Who discovered DNA double helix?"
				},
                {
                    "correct": 3,
                    "content": [
				        "actin",
				        "GAPDH",
				        "ubiquitin",
				        "EGFR"
				    ],
                    "question": "Which is not a housekeeping gene?"
				},
                {
                    "correct": 0,
                    "content": [
				        "cell apoptosis",
				        "transcription",
				        "RNA processing",
				        "translocation"
				    ],
                    "question": "Which are not part of the gene expression mechanism?"
				},
                {
                    "correct": 2,
                    "content": [
				        "4",
				        "5",
				        "7",
				        "6"
				    ],
                    "question": "How many stages are included in the cell cycle?"
				}
		    ]
		}


	]
}
